In today's video, I'm going to be diving
deep into my entire memecoin trading
strategy, and I'm going to be showing
you guys the complete ins and outs of
how a professional memecoin trader scans
and turns a low port into multiple six
figures,
>> gentlemen. So, check it out.
>> Now, if you are new here, please do not
click away. I know a lot of that might
sound very [__] cliche and I know
you've probably heard it a million
times, but I am not just some random
bummy guru on the internet trying to
sell you a course because every single
bit of information that I'm going to
give is completely free. And this video
is pretty much going to play part two to
my full course that I posted a couple
days ago, which is also completely free.
But you don't need that video for this
one because today we are going to be
diving into my entire scalping strategy.
And I'm going to be showing you guys how
I've constantly turned 0.1 Salana ports
into 100 soul ports. I've turned one
soul ports into $100,000 ports. And I
have been doing this for 8 months
straight with this exact same strategy.
So if you just want to hear me out, tune
in, bro. I promise you by the end of
this video, you're going to have a brand
new way of thinking. You're going to
have a brand new way of trading. And
you're going to have a strategy that
works on you 100% of the [__] time.
Now, how this video is going to be
structured is there's going to be four
layers to it and four different points
that I'm going to be going over. So, for
the first layer of the video, we're
going to be talking about how you should
be trading with your port size. So, if
you have a 0.1 soul port, this is how
you should be trading. If you have a one
soul port, this is how you should be
trading, etc. But we'll go over that
later. In the second part of the video,
we're going to be talking about trading
psychology and why it's one of the most
[__] important things in crypto
history.
I promise you, you will not ever become
profitable without hearing about
psychology and being able to control
your emotions. So, please hear me out on
that one. That [__] is [__] serious.
The third level that we're going to be
going over is how to spot good
narratives, how to scalp them, how to
buy at the right time, and sell at the
right time. I'm going to be showing you
guys all of that. And the fourth level
that we're going to be talking about is
scaling your port. So, what I mean is
bringing your port up from 0.1 soul to
three or four soul. And then you can
bring that three or four soul up to 10
soul and you can keep scaling like that.
I've done it multiple times. My most
recent video is me turning 0.1 Salana
into three Salana using this exact
strategy I'm going to be going over
today. And if you don't believe me, feel
free pause this video, go watch my last
one. I have that full strategy and I'm
using it the entire time. And with using
the strategy, I have constant months
where I'm making 10 to $15,000 trading
meme coins. There are literally months
where I do not lose, not even in a
single day. I am always making money
with the strategy. I'm not going to put
you guys on no [__] I'm not going
to gatekeep anything from anybody. And
again, I'm not selling you guys
anything. And this is information that
you would not get taught if you went and
bought a paid course. So trust me, boys.
I'm about to spit some [__]
knowledge.
So, lock the [__] in, boys. If you're
really serious about this and you really
want to take it serious and make it your
full-time job, grab your notebook and
we're going to get right into it. I hope
you fellas enjoy this one and we're
going to get right into it. Enjoy
Brody's.
>> Step one, trading with a low portfolio.
Get your money up, not your [__]
funny up.
>> All right, so the first thing that I
want to talk about in today's video is
evaporating all of the dog [__] that is
going to find you when you first load up
Axiom or whatever trading terminal
you're using. So, I went over this in my
last video, but to all the people that
are new here, I'm going to go over it
again. And I also had a lot of people
joining my Discord and they had no idea
what I was even talking about. They had
no idea about the filters that I pointed
out. So, I'm going to go over it quickly
again. So, whenever you load up Axiom or
whatever trading terminal you use, your
page is not going to look like mine.
It's going to be filled with complete
dog [__] And I'm just going to show you
how to get rid of all that. So, when you
first load up, your page is going to
look very similar to this. And what
you're going to notice is there's going
to be a lot of scam tokens coming out in
the new pairs. So, I can already see
one. We can see Niche Baby. This is at
300 million market cap, but it is a scam
coin. This is a Meteora launchpad
launched on a completely different
website than Pump Fun. So basically what
these tokens are for is they're luring
in beginners that have no idea what they
are doing and you really can't tell
what's a scam coin and what isn't. So a
beginner might look at a token like this
and see, wow, this coin is at 400
million. It's going to billions. Let me
buy into it. And then bang, you realize
you can't sell and you just lost all of
your money. So a very simple and easy
way to get around looking at all these
dog [__] tokens and we're just going to
get rid of them. So we are only trading
good coins that we can make money on is
what you want to do is above your new
pairs final stretch and migrated you
will see these little filter tabs. And
once you click on your filters tabs you
are going to be met with all these
launchpads and all you need to do is
click on unselect all and then select
pump fun. Now the reason we are getting
rid of all these other launchpads is
because 99% of them have zero volume or
they are just a [__] scam and we are
only trying to trade tokens that are
going to make us rich. This is very
basic stuff, but I still feel like I
need to go over it again just in case a
couple people missed it. So, whenever
you load up, please, I beg you, so you
don't fall into any traps, come over to
the filters page, unselect all these
launchpads, and only click on pump fun,
please. I'm just asking you to do this
one thing. And once you have that, you
can just click apply. And make sure you
do it for your final stretch as well.
So, you would come over to here, click
unselect all, and then pump fund. And
for your migrated, this is really
optional because we aren't going to be
trading migrated tokens. But if you want
to, if you want to feel a little bit
safer, it's totally up to you. You can
come over here and unselect all of these
and only click on pump fund. I don't do
it because I don't even [__] around with
migrated. But if you want to do that,
bro, that's totally fine. It's totally
up to you. Now, for the second part of
cleaning up our page, we're just going
to put on a couple of filters to make
sure we're not getting filled up with
all these [__] dog [__] tokens coming
out. Millions of them coming out every
second. And trust me, when you are new,
you do not want to be over stimulated.
You are going to get really confused
really fast. So, make sure you pay
attention right here. The first thing is
you want to come over to the new pairs,
click on the filters tab, and then you
want to scroll down and click on
metrics. And then you want to find the
market cap and type in 7,000 minimum
market cap. So, once you have done that,
you can just click apply all. And you
are going to notice your new pairs is
100 times cleaner than it was before.
Sometimes there will even be no tokens
in it. But the reason that we put on
7,000 minimum is because we are only
trying to find brand new tokens that are
getting volume, that are actually
getting real people buying into them.
And we are trying to make sure you do
not get licked because I promise you,
people are praying on your downfall.
They're trying to put you into that
[__] diddy pack. So, when you are
new, make sure you put that setting on.
I promise you, it's going to make life
so much [__] easier. And for the last
part of cleaning up our screen is we
want to come over to final stretch. Then
you want to come down to audit and you
want to type in age max 40 minutes. and
make sure this little dropown box is in
the M, not the S in hours. Then you want
to come down, type in maximum five for
the dev holding percentage. Then you
want to scroll even more down, find
insiders percentage, and type in maximum
20. And for the last part of the audit,
you want to type in prot traders minimum
10. And for the last part of our
filters, we just want to come to
metrics, find market cap, and type in
minimum 8,000. Now, if that was way too
much information, way too fast, and you
guys kind of needed to pause through it,
don't worry. There's a very easy way, so
you don't have to keep rewinding. All
you need to do is go to my link in the
description. Join my Discord. It's
completely free. All the tools in here
are completely free and you'll find this
filters channel right here where I have
all my filters pre-saved. So, you don't
need to keep coming back to this video
to find them. They are all set right in
here and they never change. All right,
fellas. So, now that we have cleaned up
our screen, the next part that I want to
talk about is what you should be buying,
what you should be looking for, and what
kind of tokens you should be bidding.
So, normally when you are scanning
either new pairs or final stretch, you
are going to come across three different
types of tokens. And what these tokens
are going to be is they're going to be
tweets, communities, and profiles. And
what I mean by those three is when
somebody takes a posted tweet they got
from Twitter and they link it to their
Pump Fund coin. And normally these tweet
coins are consisting of thesis and
speculation. Now, let me ask you
something. If you were trading on a very
low port and you really don't want to
lose any money, would you want to be
trading on pure speculation? Obviously,
[__] not. That's why we aren't going
to be trading tweets. But for the second
kind of coin that you are going to be
looking at is profile coins. And these
ones are usually the worst ones that you
can possibly pick. So on the screen
right now, this is what a profiled coin
would look like with that little blue
guy logo. 99% of the time, these profile
coins are built on somebody trying to
launch a project, but 99% of them are
all LAP. And the last type of coin that
we are going to be talking about and the
one that we are going to focus on is
community tokens. Now, I have talked
about community coins multiple times in
past videos and told you guys why you
should only be trading them. But the
reason that you should be trading
community coins over any other token is
because community coins are built on an
actual community. And I'm going to show
you guys how to identify these good
community coins, how to get in early,
how to scalp them, and what a good
community token looks like. So, when you
are scanning trying to find a good
community token, there are four main
checks that you need to be doing when
you find the correct token and deciding
whether or not you want to put your
hard-earned KFC shift into this meme
coin. So, the first thing that you need
to be doing, and you need to make this a
muscle memory every single time you
click on any token, you need to be doing
these checks. Otherwise, you are going
to get destroyed. You are going to lose
all of your money. So, please make sure
you are doing these checks. So, let's
say this random coin Bible miss is our
community token. We really like the
narrative. We really want to put our
hard-earned money into it, but we need
to do our checks to see if it really
suits what we want to buy. So, the first
check that you need to be doing is you
need to come down to the holders page.
And once you click on the holders page,
and you need to be looking for the top
five holders, and we're going to be
looking for any types of signs that this
is a bundle, a multi-wallet, or just
fake volume. So, the first check that
you do when you're looking at the top
five holders is you want to be looking
at the Salana balance on these holders.
So I can see the number one holder, he
has five soul in his balance. The second
three soul, the fourth one soul, and the
fifth 4.7 salana. Now this is really
important because I'm going to show you
guys an example of what a bundled
holding balance would look like. And if
it was bundled, all of these Salana
balances would be very, very, very
similar. So what I mean is this wouldn't
say five soul, three soul, one soul, one
soul, four soul. It would much more look
something like what's up on screen right
now. and it would say.1 soul.1 soul.1
soul.1 soul.1 soul all the way down and
that is a complete bundle. It's a very
easy way to check if your coin is
bundled. So please make sure you guys
understand how important this check is.
You need to be doing it every single
time. Do not skip over it. It is going
to save you so much money. Now the
second check that we are doing on our
top five holders is we're seeing where
these wallets are being funded from. So
I'm going to be looking at the top five.
And the top five starts right below the
liquidity pool. And we have the number
one holder, number two, number three,
number four, and number five. And what
we are looking at here is similar
wallets that they are being funded from.
So already I can see the number one
wallet is an Axiom signup wallet. Second
is a regular signup wallet. The third is
another regular signup wallet. And the
rest for the other two. But the real
important detail right here that you
need to be looking for is the dates that
these have been funded from. But we can
see 6 days ago, 22 days ago, 3 years
ago, 7 months ago, and 2 days ago. And
this is very [__] important. I'm
going to show you guys another example
of what a bundled funding time wallets
will look like. And it would not look
like this. The date will be very
similar. It will say something like
funded 1 day ago, 1 day ago, 1 day ago,
or funded an hour ago, an hour ago, an
hour ago. Please make sure you're doing
this check. It's going to save you so
much money. I swear to God, I wish I
knew these [__] checks when I
started. But just like a lot of you
guys, I had no idea what the [__] I was
doing. So, please make sure you're
paying attention. Write the [__] down,
screenshot it, rewind it, and really get
it into your brain and make this a
muscle memory check that you were doing
every single day. Now, the second check
that we're going to do on our community
tokens is very obvious, yet a lot of
people still somehow miss it. And you
wouldn't believe what the step is. The
step that we are going to be checking on
our community token is we're checking
the community.
Isn't that [__] insane? I know a lot
of people don't even do this, which just
blows my mind. But what we need to do is
come over to the top left, click on this
little community page, and when we're in
the community page, there are three
checks that we need to be doing as well.
So, for the first check is we want to be
making sure the CA is in the description
or the bio of the community. So, right
here is where the CA is meant to be in
the description of the community, but I
can't see it anywhere. So, that is our
first [__] red flag. If I see that,
I'm gone. I'm out of that [__] Now,
our second check is seeing if there is a
pin tweet in the community with a C
attached to it. So, normally at the very
very top right here, there will be a pin
post with the CA and what the narrative
is. If there isn't one of those, that's
also a red flag. I always stay away from
that [__] And for the final check, we
want to be making sure there's actual
[__] human beings talking in here.
So, we're clicking on the latest and
we're basically seeing if there's any
activity in the community. So, on the
first post I see, there's just a [__]
link. You don't want people sending
links in your community. That shows
there's no moderation. You don't want
any risk of people sending like drainers
into a community link. That's no
moderation. It's dog [__] It's another
huge red flag. So, right here, this
community is dog [__] So, we have no CA
in the description. We have no pin tweet
at the top. We have no CA coming from
the admin of the community. And there's
like nobody talking in the community.
They're just sending random links and
sending random dog [__] posts. So, all
three of those are red flags. If you
actually find those in your community,
if you find a pin post, a CA in the
description, you see people tweeting
about it, talking about it, there's
activity in it, then that's a very good
sign and you should use that to push
your buyers.
So right here on the screen we are
looking at two different charts that
I've drawn up and these are very very
common chart patterns that you're going
to be seeing like 90% of the time. These
are the two chart patterns that you're
going to be looking at. On the left side
we have a bundled chart and on the right
side we have a clean chart. And it is
very very easy to spot out what a bundle
chart looks like. It might be a little
bit confusing at first but hear me out.
I'm going to simplify it, make you guys
understand it. It's really simple. And
then we're going to get right into when
you should be buying and selling and how
to be scalping these tokens. So for our
first chart, this is our bundle chart.
And you are going to be seeing this
chart millions of times when you are
clicking on tokens. So right here on the
screen, I've marked out 5K market
cap/aunch. And this is when the token
launches. So the floor is set at 5K.
This is where the dev is going to be
buying and holding his supply. And what
we want to be looking for is the price
action that comes in right as the dev
launches. So, a very easy way that we
can check for a bundle to tell whether
or not a chart is about to get [__]
demolished on your dome piece or not is
by looking at what the price does as
soon as the coin launches on top of the
dev. So, right here at the very bottom,
we are at 5k market cap. This is where
the dev is going to be buying. And all
we can see is a big big [__] candle
only straight up. And we are going to be
marking this out as like 10k market cap.
So, it is just one big green candle from
5k to 10k. no sells, no other price
action, nothing. And I'm going to show
you guys a real example of this on a
real chart. It's very easy to spot, but
what this shows is a bundle getting into
it or a multi-wallet getting into it.
They are all buying supply at the very
bottom, at the very lowest they possibly
can, holding it to the top. And what
they are going to do is they are going
to slowly clip out of it maybe once at a
time to try and make it look like real
human behavior. So right here we can see
a little tiny nuke. And this right here
is where normal people start getting
into it. They're buying off that little
bundle clip and they are creating real
volume, but the bundle right here is
still holding all of the [__] supply.
So right here, this is a real example of
what I was just talking about. We can
see the big fat green candle all the way
up. We can see the dev launches at 4K
market cap. The big fat [__] green
candle all the way to 12K. This is
exactly what I was just talking about,
word for word, in real time. And what is
going to happen to the coin? The bundle
gets in, they pump it all the way up to
14K from 4K market cap and then they are
going to sell it right here. Try and
create some real human psychology
behavior. And then real people are going
to buy it. And what happens after real
people buy it? The bundle nukes it. This
happens literally hundreds and hundreds
and hundreds of times a day. And you
guys really need to know how this [__]
works because I promise you without
knowing this, you are going to get
destroyed. Do not skip over this. I know
you really just want to learn how to
scalp, how to buy at the right time, and
how to sell. But this is very very
[__] important. So if you are
skipping over this, I promise you,
you're going to get destroyed. But make
sure you know what this looks like. You
are going to get demolished if you don't
understand this. And you might be
thinking, set up, what if there is a
chart that does that exact pattern, but
it keeps going up? How do I identify
that is a bundle? Trust me, if it ever
forms that pattern that we just talked
about, it is a bundle and there is
always a way to prove it is. So, just
like that holder method that we were
talking about right before and I was
telling you guys to make sure always
check the Salana balance on the holders
and always check where they are being
funded from. If we just scroll down and
do our holders check from before, we can
see our soul balance on our holders is
completely [__] We can see 0.02
0.1.03
0.1.
And if that isn't enough evidence for
you, we can look at the funding time. We
have 25 minutes ago, 25, 25, 9 months,
25, 25, 25, 25, 25, 25. I cannot stress
this [__] enough, boys. If you aren't
listening and paying attention to this
[__] you are going to get [__]
destroyed. I'm trying to save you guys
your money. I'm being completely for
real. There is nothing more serious you
need to take than understanding how to
identify these [__] scam tokens.
Because when I was brand new, I had no
idea what I was doing. And I wish I had
somebody like me to tell me how this
[__] worked. So, now that we have gotten
up to this point, we have learned
everything about our filters. We have
learned how to identify a bundle, and we
have learned every green flag and red
flag you should be looking out for when
you're scanning these community tokens.
And now, what we are going to get into
is I know you guys have been waiting for
this. We're going to talk about how you
should be buying and selling these
tokens, how you should be scalping them,
what price you buy, what price you sell,
and we're going to go over all of that.
So, put on your [__] seat belt,
fellas, because this might get a little
confusing, but I'm going to try and
simplify it all so you guys have a very
easy time understanding. And let's get
right into scalping. So, when you were
scanning and you were looking to scalp,
you have all your filters set up. What
you should be looking for is the coins
at the very bottom of Final Stretch.
Now, the reason I don't trade the coins
at the very top of Final Stretch is
because they were already pretty old.
They are already a higher market cap.
And the scalps that you are going to
find at higher market caps are going to
be way way smaller than the ones that
you're going to find at smaller market
cap. So the tokens that I focus on in
Final Stretch and new pairs is every
single coin in new pairs and pretty much
the bottom four of Final Stretch. So I
normally always stay away from the top
two. You can still trade the top two if
you want to, but it's really just
personal preference of what I found has
worked. So let's say we want to scalp
this coin right here, Middle Finger. It
has a community attached to it. It's
free of all bundles. you've done all
your checks on it and all around you
just think the narrative is funny. Where
would we be looking to buy and sell this
coin? So for me right here, I already
know where I would be looking to buy and
sell. And as much as I say TA does not
[__] exist in meme coins, there is
still a little bit of TA, but it's not
technical analysis. It's more psychology
zones. So in my last course video, I
taught you guys about the 40% dip
method, which still works every single
time. So you can see right here, this
coin spawned in at 4K market cap. It ran
all the way up to 10K and what did it
do? It dipped 44% and got bought right
back up. Now, this dip method is so easy
and beginner friendly to do, but I'm
still going to teach you guys some more
[__] about scalping so you don't have to
only rely on this. So, when we're
talking about scalping, there is a big
thing that I really want you guys to
know, and this is not getting married to
your tokens. I honestly pretty much want
all of you guys to treat your money like
if you lose your money, you are going to
die. You have to be a Jeet. And what I
mean is as soon as that [__] drops below
your average price, you need to be
selling that [__] Now, in my trading
video, I did multiple examples of this.
As soon as it went down below my average
price, I was full stacking out of it. I
don't want to lose money, and we can't
take that gamble of maybe the coin will
come back up. We just can't take that
risk. Let's say we want to scalp this
coin right here. It's currently at 40K.
Where would I be looking to buy this
[__] Now, this is a very, very simple
chart pattern, but this chart pattern
will work every single time. Every time
you buy the dip on this chart pattern,
you are going to make money. So, when
you dealing with these coins that are
all the way up at like 40k market cap,
you do not want to be buying these
little 10% dips. So, what I mean is if a
coin is at 40k market cap and we only
dip about 10% to 30k market cap, that is
not enough sell pressure for people to
get interested in buying it. Again, we
really want to be looking for the people
that want the best entries. Meme coins
is all psychology and all these people
want the lowest entry possible. So when
a no bundled good narrative coin runs
all the way up to 40k and that [__]
takes a fat [__] plummet. This [__]
nukes all the way back down straight to
20k from 40, what do you think people
are going to do? They are going to be
buying that dip. And I'm going to show
you guys an example of this. So right
here on this coin, middle finger, the
one that we were just talking about. We
can see this went all the way up to 60K
and people are getting disinterested in
buying this coin because it's still
sitting around 40k. That's not low
enough for them to want to buy into it.
And what every single person is waiting
for is that big 40 to 50% nuke on that
coin to buy into it. So right here,
right, we went to all-time high 58K. We
dipped all the way back down to 45% dip.
And what happens after we dip down 45%
from an all-time high every single time,
people are going to buy it back up
another 45%. This [__] happens every
single [__] time. If you have a good
community, the bundle is clean, you
don't have a [__] ton of tracked wallets
in it, then this is going to work for
you like a gem. I swear to God, I do
this [__] all the time.
So, now I want to talk about because I
get this question asked to me a lot in
my Discord and a lot of people ask me,
how much should I be buying with
depending on my port? And don't worry, I
got you guys covered on the most you
should be buying with depending on your
port. So when you were looking to scalp
these 40% dips on the new pairs and the
final stretch, if you have a 0.1 Salana
port, you should only be aping in 0.05
on a new pairs by the absolute maximum
0.07 on final stretch scalping. This way
on a 0.1 Salana port, you don't get
demolished on fees and you can still
make some good money. If that [__] 2xes
or gives you a 50%, that's still a good
bit of money to build up your port. Now,
if you have a 0.5 Salana port, the max
you should be doing is 0.1 Salana buys
on new pairs. And for final stretch, you
should be doing 2 Salana buys. Do not go
lower. Do not go higher. I promise you,
if you are still going lower and you
have a.5 soul port, you will just being
very stingy and scared. So, grow some
nuts, bro, and start aping in a little
bit more. Now, if you have a one Salana
port, the most you should be doing on
new pairs is 0.25 25 Salana and the max
you should be doing on final stretch is
04 Salana. I promise you you want to be
doing this amount of buys. When I have a
0.1 soul port and I'm trying to build it
up to five soul, 10 soul, I never go
over these. And for the final port size
that you should be doing, I know this is
probably a rare one that not many people
watching this will have. But if you are
trading with a five Salana port, you
should be doing max one soul buys on 40%
dips on new pairs and 1.5 soul on the
final stretch. Now, this is very
adjustable depending on your trading
style. If you want to use more, it's
completely up to you on these higher
ports. For the lower ports, please just
stick with what I said. Don't go lower.
Don't go higher. Now, you might be
wondering, Seda, I only have a 0.01
Salana port. What do I do? I'm going to
be honest. If you have a 0.01 port or
you have a port lower than.1 Salana, you
shouldn't be trading meme coins. You are
going to get demolished by fees. I'm
sorry. It's the harsh truth. I know a
lot of people won't tell you this
because a lot of people will just lie to
you and say you can turn $1 into a
million dollars, but trading meme coins,
it is just not [__] true. So, if you
have a $1 port, please just like go get
a [__] job at McDonald's. Go drive
for Door Dash. Go get your money up
somehow. [snorts] Beg your mom for some
Christmas money, but trading with a $1
port is not going to cut it. I'm very
sorry to disappoint all you fellas
trading with $1 ports, but that [__] is
just not going to cut it. But for the
rest, please do not switch up on those
ports that I've gave you and how much
you should be buying with. Screenshot
those, stick with them. And yeah, man.
Now, something I also want to go over
quick is a lot of people ask me, "How do
I find the perfect narrative? How do I
find the greatest narratives?" And
honestly, this is a question that I
cannot just give to you because it
honestly just takes time. The best
teacher for finding good narratives and
coins is time. You have to be staring at
the new pairs. You have to be staring at
Final Stretch all day, every day. And
you are going to build the skill that
helps you find tokens. The best teacher
for finding good tokens is time. I
cannot just tell you, oh, if it has this
and this in the name, it is a good
token. No, because this [__] changes
every single day. But again, I can teach
you in a way to spot these coins,
dissect them, and build your bias to
whether or not it's a good narrative to
you. I promise you, I'm keeping it 100%
real. And if you don't like this answer,
if you want me to just tell you buy this
coin and it's going to 100x, then you
are in the wrong [__] place cuz I'm
not that person that's going to tell you
that. And also, one more thing that I
want to run over is a lot of people will
probably be asking me, "What about the
fees? What about this? What about that?"
I went over all of my fees and all the
beginner stuff in my previous course
video that has jam-packed information
full of beginner stuff. It has fees,
wallet tracking, all of that. So, if you
want more information on that, feel
free. Go watch my entire course on
YouTube. This was pretty much just a
part two of how I find my strategy, how
I scout these coins, what I'm looking
for, how to dissect the bundles, and how
to make some [__] money on on meme
coins, fellas. But I hope you have found
some value in this video, man. I pretty
much tried to give you all the
information that I know on this YouTube
channel. So, if you found some value,
bro, please feel free hit that [__]
subscribe button. I really appreciate
it. And if you want some more tools and
you want to be trading with multiple
people, go to the link in my
description, join my Discord. is
completely free and I will be back very
very soon with another live trading
video. So I hope you fellas enjoy this
one and peace out broies.
Check
my [music] pants.